[{"question":"which object is bigger?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The concrete cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The marble cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"What is the material of the large cube?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"Porcelain"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"Concrete"}],"answer":1},{"question":"How many cubes there?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"3"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"4"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which object has lower density?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The small bamboo cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The small brick cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Is the large concrete cube heavier than the small bamboo cube?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which object has lower friction?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The small bamboo cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The small marble cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which object has larger restitution?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The small brick cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The large concrete cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which quadrant will the small brick cube be in when it finally stops moving ?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"\u2160"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"\u2161"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"\u2162"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"\u2163"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which quadrant will the large concrete cube be in when it finally stops moving ?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"\u2160"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"\u2161"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"\u2162"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"\u2163"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which object will stop moving earlier?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The large concrete cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The small marble cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which object will stop moving first?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The large concrete cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The small bamboo cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the small bamboo cube travel to quadrant \u2161?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will there a collision in the quadrant \u2162?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"How many collisions will happen between objects?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"<=3"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":">3"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Will the small marble cube collide more than once?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the large concrete cube collide with the wall in this video?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Will the small marble cube collide with the wall in this video?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which objects is the first collision?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The large concrete cube and the small brick cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The small brick cube and the small bamboo cube"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"The small bamboo cube and the small marble cube"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"The small marble cube and the large concrete cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which objects is the last collision?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The small bamboo cube and the small brick cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The small marble cube and the wall"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"The small marble cube and the small brick cube"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"The large concrete cube and the small bamboo cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Will the small brick cube collide with other objects after it stops moving?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":1}]